<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en_us"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en_us" /><updated>2024-04-28T21:04:32+00:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">The Daily Grift</title><author><name>Alx</name></author><entry><title type="html">Gamedev Is Not A Crime</title><link href="/gamedev-is-not-a-crime/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Gamedev Is Not A Crime" /><published>2024-03-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-03-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/gamedev-is-not-a-crime</id><content type="html" xml:base="/gamedev-is-not-a-crime/"><![CDATA[<p>Have you ever noticed that there are countless Pong, or Snake, or Froggie clones in the app stores and game stores like Itch.io or Steam ?</p>

<p>The proliferation of those games is taking place because they are the first test games that any aspiring developer starts from. They are the proving grounds for most of us who start experimenting in this wonderfull world and those games will be the first modded works that their developers will work on.</p>

<p>They’re not meant to be full, complete, buggless or anything. The only function they carry is helping a developer learn the ropes. Now, is that all it takes ?
Obviously not. I made a Pong clone uning Python classes, one with Pygame, one with GDevelop, one with UPBGE and now I’m working on one in Unity. I find it to be a great tool that allows me as a noob to gauge how good of an understanding I have of various concepts.</p>

<p>I also did that with my programming languages journey. When I would learn to do a new thing in Python, I would then repeat the same thing in C++ or C.</p>

<p>PS I’m trying to get into jQuery these days, without a functioning knowledge of Javascript. This should be illegal…</p>]]></content><author><name>alx</name></author><category term="Rants" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever noticed that there are countless Pong, or Snake, or Froggie clones in the app stores and game stores like Itch.io or Steam ?]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/8.webp" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/images/8.webp" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Unfazed By War</title><link href="/unfazed-by-war/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Unfazed By War" /><published>2024-03-14T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-03-14T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/unfazed-by-war</id><content type="html" xml:base="/unfazed-by-war/"><![CDATA[<p>War, the master engineer of humanity. The greatest plight and solution of last -or first for some- resort. Wars are changing in the 21st century.</p>

<p>From the AI powered drones wreaking havoc to the Russian invaders of Ukrainian lands to the non-kinetic force that Bitcoin projects, the future of war is being redrawn.</p>

<p>Stack harder anon, this future looks bleak.</p>]]></content><author><name>alx</name></author><category term="Rants" /><category term="News" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[War, the master engineer of humanity. The greatest plight and solution of last -or first for some- resort. Wars are changing in the 21st century.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/7.webp" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/images/7.webp" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Whale Feeding Grounds</title><link href="/whale-feeding-grounds/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Whale Feeding Grounds" /><published>2024-03-02T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-03-02T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/whale-feeding-grounds</id><content type="html" xml:base="/whale-feeding-grounds/"><![CDATA[<p>It would make sense, wouldn’t it ? We’re a species that thrives in social circumstances. So, we all love seeing a comeback, either an underdog claiming a rightful spot or a green dildo. Bitcoin loves its green dildoes more than it loves stability. It thrives in volatility and so do we speculators.</p>

<p>The trend is your friend. Learning how to read the weather is an essential skill for any sailor, surfer or pilot. It could not be different for plebs riding the waves in this irrational market.</p>

<h2 id="do-you-want-to-feel-the-waves-">Do you want to feel the waves ?</h2>

<p>That’s all you have to ask yourself and dive right in.</p>

<p>You can dive in the testnet if you’re so inclined but really, is there a better rush than feeling the whales breathing down your back while you’re scalping buys in front of them at x100 ?</p>

<p>No, there isn’t and that’s why you’re a degenerate dark tetrad looking for a shortcut to the fucking moon.</p>]]></content><author><name>alx</name></author><category term="Rants" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[It would make sense, wouldn’t it ? We’re a species that thrives in social circumstances. So, we all love seeing a comeback, either an underdog claiming a rightful spot or a green dildo. Bitcoin loves its green dildoes more than it loves stability. It thrives in volatility and so do we speculators.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/1.webp" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/images/1.webp" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Riding The Red Waves</title><link href="/riding-the-red-waves/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Riding The Red Waves" /><published>2024-02-28T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-02-28T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/riding-the-red-waves</id><content type="html" xml:base="/riding-the-red-waves/"><![CDATA[<p>Sometimes the markets don’t go the way you want them. It’s okay, we’ve all been there. In fact, you MUST get there if you want to reach the moon in due time. Learning to deal with problems and liquidations is one of the most important aspects of trading.</p>

<p>It’s hard to resist the FOMO, but fear not for I will teach you the Art Of Zen in the land of Falling Knives.</p>

<p>I remember one time, I was part of a trading bot beta team, so before each release we’d receive the updated algo to go ahead and try it. So I armed it with my strategy, gave it its marching orders and sent it off to take over the Poloniex markets. Unaware, I looked after it for a bit and went on with my daily chores. Oh boy…</p>

<p>So, back then <a href="https://poloniex.com">Poloniex</a> had decent volumes, a nice shitcoin portfolio and an awesome lending market. So I had a trading bot running the markets and a lending bot lending out coins to speculators, it was awesome. But, unbeknownst to me, the trading bot was flawed. It had an issue in its logic. It was illogical.</p>

<p>I came back a few hours later to find 2.5 BTC spread in over 20 shitcoins. It was devastating and painful.</p>

<p>Eventually, and luckily for me, the market recovered and I more than quadrupled those coins in that month. But only because I was lucky. I decided that algos needed to be better overwatched by yours truly and that I should never let one manage the trades on its own.</p>]]></content><author><name>alx</name></author><category term="Trading" /><category term="Tips" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes the markets don’t go the way you want them. It’s okay, we’ve all been there. In fact, you MUST get there if you want to reach the moon in due time. Learning to deal with problems and liquidations is one of the most important aspects of trading.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/4.webp" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/images/4.webp" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Waiting For Summer</title><link href="/waiting-for-summer/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Waiting For Summer" /><published>2024-02-16T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-02-16T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/waiting-for-summer</id><content type="html" xml:base="/waiting-for-summer/"><![CDATA[<p>As the Bull Season (TM) is approaching many are feeling the FOMO. I’ve been here since 2013 and let me tell you, there is nothing quite like it. Especially if you lack the absolute minimum of self-respect.</p>

<p>The idea that yuo can spend $1 and become a gazillionaire overnight is overwhelming, more so among the plebs. So how do you do it ?</p>

<p>Enter x100. Add a touch of degeneracy, sprinkle it with Discrete Log Contracts and Bitcoin and you have something going.</p>

<p>Pair it with instant settlement on the Lightning Network and we’re golden baby, let’s send this rocket to the moon !</p>]]></content><author><name>alx</name></author><category term="Cope" /><category term="Rants" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the Bull Season (TM) is approaching many are feeling the FOMO. I’ve been here since 2013 and let me tell you, there is nothing quite like it. Especially if you lack the absolute minimum of self-respect.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/3.webp" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/images/3.webp" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Debugging The Bull</title><link href="/debugging-the-bull/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Debugging The Bull" /><published>2024-01-22T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-01-22T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/debugging-the-bull</id><content type="html" xml:base="/debugging-the-bull/"><![CDATA[<p>I always felt intrigued by <code>code</code>. It felt like the people who delved into its secrets held the keys to the magical kingdom of do-whatever-you-feel-like. And it really is like that, as Satoshi proved. He used merely 200k lines of C++ and rewrote the future.</p>

<p>And the plebs took that and memed a world reserve currency in existence. The lesson is clear: Don’t mess with the deranged.</p>

<p>Code snippets are always fun, even if they’re mostly useless:</p>

<figure class="highlight"><pre><code class="language-ruby" data-lang="ruby"><span class="k">def</span> <span class="nf">print_hi</span><span class="p">(</span><span class="nb">name</span><span class="p">)</span>
  <span class="nb">puts</span> <span class="s2">"Hi, </span><span class="si">#{</span><span class="nb">name</span><span class="si">}</span><span class="s2">"</span>
<span class="k">end</span>
<span class="n">print_hi</span><span class="p">(</span><span class="s1">'Satoshi'</span><span class="p">)</span>
<span class="c1">#=&gt; prints 'Hi, Satoshi' to STDOUT.</span></code></pre></figure>

<p>Fun. Code is fun, even if sometimes it’s merely a black box.</p>]]></content><author><name>alx</name></author><category term="Algos" /><category term="Code" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[I always felt intrigued by code. It felt like the people who delved into its secrets held the keys to the magical kingdom of do-whatever-you-feel-like. And it really is like that, as Satoshi proved. He used merely 200k lines of C++ and rewrote the future.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/6.webp" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/images/6.webp" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">x100 To The Moon</title><link href="/x100-to-the-moon/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="x100 To The Moon" /><published>2024-01-12T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-01-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/x100-to-the-moon</id><content type="html" xml:base="/x100-to-the-moon/"><![CDATA[<p>The first time I heard about Bitcoin, i was like “GTFO, computer money can’t work”. Since then I realized many shared the same first reaction. I guess it’s only natural. But since then, it has been a decade, and we know more about this unique form of technology.</p>

<p>I made my first million by 23 and lost it by 24, all thanks to Bitcoin, FOMO and hype. But I learned and I am stronger, a pleb among plebs. While WW3 is flaring up, we memed a world reserve currency in existence. Are you not entertained ?</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>If you don’t believe me or dont get it, I dont have time to convince you, sorry</p>
</blockquote>

<p>Let’s get x100 to the moon!</p>]]></content><author><name>alx</name></author><category term="bitcoin" /><category term="rants" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first time I heard about Bitcoin, i was like “GTFO, computer money can’t work”. Since then I realized many shared the same first reaction. I guess it’s only natural. But since then, it has been a decade, and we know more about this unique form of technology.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/2.webp" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/images/2.webp" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">History Rhymes, Doesn’t Repeat</title><link href="/history-rhymes-doesnt-repeat/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="History Rhymes, Doesn’t Repeat" /><published>2023-12-27T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-12-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/history-rhymes-doesnt-repeat</id><content type="html" xml:base="/history-rhymes-doesnt-repeat/"><![CDATA[<p>I’m not even going to try to pretend that I can make sense of what’s been happening in the last five years. And I don’t mean just <mark>Bitcoin</mark>.</p>

<p>I mean the “Two Weeks To Flatten The Curve” that drove so many people mad. Three years later and I can see people going completley off the rails.</p>

<p>Conspiracies are everywhere now and “They” control every aspect of life. The smoothbrains have taken over social media, made groups, are lobbying and even have people in national parliaments.</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>We are prone to let our mental life become invaded by legions of half truths, prejudices, and propaganda. At this point, I often wonder whether or not education is fulfilling its purpose. A great majority of the so-called educated people do not think logically and scientifically.</p>
</blockquote>

<p>Can we come out of this rabbit hole of stupidity ?</p>]]></content><author><name>alx</name></author><category term="News" /><category term="Cope" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m not even going to try to pretend that I can make sense of what’s been happening in the last five years. And I don’t mean just Bitcoin.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/5.webp" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/images/5.webp" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry></feed>