<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en_us"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en_us" /><updated>2024-05-12T22:10:56+00:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">The Daily Grift</title><author><name>Alx</name></author><entry><title type="html">Deciphering The Ripple Effects</title><link href="/deciphering-the-ripple-effects/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Deciphering The Ripple Effects" /><published>2024-04-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-04-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/deciphering-the-ripple-effects</id><content type="html" xml:base="/deciphering-the-ripple-effects/"><![CDATA[<p>This is Part Two of my armchair analysis on short term speculator sentiment following the halving. It was preceded by <a href="/speculating-on-algorithmic-scarcity/">Part One, that you can find here.</a></p>

<p>This part concludes a fast and dirty analysis. You should take what I say here with a giant lump of salt because I trade with that knowledge succesfully but I can’t be held liable for your mistakes in this irrational market.</p>

<h2 id="post-halving-hodler-behavior">Post-Halving Hodler Behavior</h2>

<p>The Bitcoin halving event not only alters the mining landscape and market dynamics but also significantly impacts investor behavior.</p>

<p>This section explores how different market participants have adjusted their strategies, the influx of new hodlers, and the prevailing sentiments that are shaping the market’s future.</p>

<h3 id="bitcoin-hodlers-adapting-their-strategies">Bitcoin Hodlers Adapting Their Strategies</h3>

<p>The reduction in mining rewards and the subsequent price fluctuations have prompted Bitcoin hodlers to reassess their investment strategies.</p>

<p>Many long-term hodlers are strengthening their positions by accumulating more Bitcoins during price dips, a strategy known as “buying the dip”.</p>

<p>This approach is based on the expectation that the value of Bitcoin will increase in the long term as the supply becomes more limited.</p>

<p>On the other hand, some traders are capitalizing on the increased volatility by engaging in short-term speculative trading. Speculators are thriving in this environment.</p>

<p>These hodlers are less concerned with the long-term prospects of Bitcoin price action and more interested in leveraging short-term price movements for profit.</p>

<h3 id="new-entrants-in-the-market-and-their-impact">New Entrants in the Market and Their Impact</h3>

<p>The halving event has also attracted new entrants into the Bitcoin market, drawn by the media coverage and the potential for substantial returns.</p>

<p>These newcomers include both retail and institutional hodlers, each bringing different perspectives and expectations to the market.</p>

<p>Retail hodlers often enter the market with less experience and are more susceptible to market sentiments and trends, which can lead to increased volatility.</p>

<p>In contrast, institutional hodlers bring larger capital inflows and a focus on long-term value, which can help stabilize and legitimize the market.</p>

<h3 id="hodler-sentiment-and-market-speculations">Hodler Sentiment and Market Speculations</h3>

<p>Hodler sentiment following the Bitcoin halving is a mix of optimism and caution. The optimism stems from the historical performance of Bitcoin post-halving, where prices have
generally increased significantly over the following years.</p>

<p>Many hodlers remain bullish, viewing the current price dips as temporary setbacks in the broader context of a long-term bull market.</p>

<p>However, there is also a palpable sense of caution among hodlers, driven by the uncertain economic climate and potential regulatory changes that could affect the cryptocurrency
market.</p>

<p>Speculations abound regarding the impact of new technologies, such as quantum computing, on the security of cryptocurrencies, including Bitcoin.</p>

<p>Overall, the behavior of hodlers post-halving is shaping the trajectory of Bitcoin’s future, influenced by a complex interplay of historical data, market sentiment, and global economic factors.</p>

<p>As the market continues to mature, these behaviors and sentiments will play a crucial role in determining the stability and growth of Bitcoin as a mainstream financial asset.</p>

<h2 id="epilogue">Epilogue</h2>

<h3 id="summary-of-key-findings">Summary of Key Findings</h3>

<p>The exploration of Bitcoin’s latest halving has revealed several critical insights:</p>

<ul>
  <li><strong>Economic Impact</strong>: The reduction in mining rewards has significant implications for miners and the broader economic environment of the cryptocurrency.</li>
</ul>

<p>While it poses challenges in terms of profitability, it also drives innovation in mining technology and energy sourcing.</p>

<ul>
  <li><strong>Market Trends</strong>: Contrary to the historical bullish trends following previous halvings, the immediate market reaction this time included a slight price drop.</li>
</ul>

<p>However, the long-term outlook remains optimistic, with expectations of price increases driven by a reduced rate of new Bitcoin entering the market.</p>

<ul>
  <li><strong>Investor Behavior</strong>: The halving has led to a shift in investment strategies among existing Bitcoin hodlers and attracted new entrants to the market.</li>
</ul>

<p>While long-term hodlers see the dip as a buying opportunity, short-term traders are leveraging the increased volatility for gains.</p>

<h3 id="potential-future-scenarios-for-bitcoin">Potential Future Scenarios for Bitcoin</h3>

<p>Looking forward, several scenarios could unfold for Bitcoin, influenced by various external and internal factors:</p>

<ol>
  <li>
    <p><strong>Increased Institutional Adoption</strong>: As Bitcoin continues to be compared to ‘digital gold’, its appeal as a hedge against inflation could lead to more widespread adoption by
institutional hodlers, potentially stabilizing and increasing its price.</p>
  </li>
  <li>
    <p><strong>Technological Advancements</strong>: Innovations in blockchain technology and the integration of quantum computing could significantly enhance Bitcoin’s utility and
security, attracting more users and hodlers.</p>
  </li>
  <li>
    <p><strong>Regulatory Environment</strong>: The future of Bitcoin could also be heavily influenced by regulatory decisions. Positive regulations may encourage more hodlers, while
restrictive policies could limit its growth.</p>
  </li>
  <li>
    <p><strong>Economic Shifts</strong>: Global economic changes, such as inflation rates, currency devaluation, and financial crises, could either enhance or diminish Bitcoin’s role as a
safe-haven asset.</p>
  </li>
</ol>

<h3 id="final-thoughts-and-recommendations-for-hodlers">Final Thoughts and Recommendations for Hodlers</h3>

<p>Hodlers should consider both the opportunities and risks presented by Bitcoin. It is advisable to adopt a balanced approach:</p>

<ul>
  <li>
    <p><strong>Diversify Investments</strong>: Avoid the pitfalls of market volatility and FOMO by diversifying your portfolio with a few options and stay clear of centralized custodians.</p>
  </li>
  <li>
    <p><strong>Stay Informed</strong>: Keep abreast of market trends, technological advancements, and regulatory changes that could impact Bitcoin’s value.</p>
  </li>
  <li>
    <p><strong>Consider Long-Term Horizons</strong>: Given Bitcoin’s historical performance post-halving, a long-term investment horizon may be beneficial for those who believe in the future
growth of cryptocurrencies.</p>
  </li>
  <li>
    <p><strong>Risk Management</strong>: Implement strategies to manage risk, such as setting stop-loss orders and only <em>risking funds that you can afford to lose</em>.</p>
  </li>
</ul>

<p><strong>Getting rekt is fun, until you’re broke.</strong></p>

<p>In conclusion, while the Bitcoin halving presents new challenges and opportunities, it remains a pivotal event that redefines the landscape for hodlers, miners, and the broader
financial market.</p>

<p>As the cryptocurrency world continues to evolve, staying informed and agile will be key to navigating future developments successfully.</p>

<p><strong>Tip:</strong> Remember to appreciate the little things in life, <strong>stay humble &amp; stack sats.</strong> And if you liked my armchair analysis you <a href="https://strike.me/warped/">can send some sats my way</a></p>]]></content><author><name>alx</name></author><category term="Analysis" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is Part Two of my armchair analysis on short term speculator sentiment following the halving. It was preceded by Part One, that you can find here.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/10.webp" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/images/10.webp" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Speculating On Algorithmic Scarcity</title><link href="/speculating-on-algorithmic-scarcity/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Speculating On Algorithmic Scarcity" /><published>2024-04-21T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-04-21T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/speculating-on-algorithmic-scarcity</id><content type="html" xml:base="/speculating-on-algorithmic-scarcity/"><![CDATA[<p>This is Part One of my armchair analysis on short term speculator sentiment following the halving. It is followed by <a href="/deciphering-the-ripple-effects/">Part Two, that you can find here.</a></p>

<p>The two pieces represent the best and analysis that an armchair analyst that trades better than Peter Schiff can give out for free.</p>

<h2 id="overview-of-bitcoin-halving">Overview of Bitcoin Halving</h2>

<p>The Bitcoin halving is a significant event in the orange world that occurs approximately every four years.</p>

<p>This mechanism, embedded in Bitcoin’s code, reduces the reward that miners receive for adding new blocks to the blockchain by half.</p>

<p>Originally set at 50 bitcoins per block when Bitcoin was launched in 2009, the reward has undergone several halvings, with the most recent adjustment bringing it down from 6.25 to 3.125 bitcoins per block.</p>

<h3 id="purpose-and-timing-of-the-recent-halving">Purpose and Timing of the Recent Halving</h3>

<p>The primary purpose of Bitcoin halving is to control inflation and extend the distribution of new bitcoins over a longer period, as the total supply is capped at 21 million coins. This scarcity is thought to contribute to Bitcoin’s value.</p>

<p>The latest halving occurred under the watchful eyes of hodlers and enthusiasts, keen to understand how this anticipated event would impact the market dynamics and the overall mining landscape.</p>

<h3 id="initial-observations-post-halving">Initial Observations Post-Halving</h3>

<p>Following the recent halving, the immediate effects were somewhat mixed.</p>

<p>Despite historical trends suggesting a potential increase in Bitcoin’s price post-halving, the price actually saw a 4% drop shortly after the event.</p>

<p>This unexpected turn has sparked a flurry of analysis and speculation among hodlers and market analysts.</p>

<p>While the long-term impact remains to be seen, the initial market reactions have provided a fertile ground for discussions regarding the future of Bitcoin and its positioning against traditional and digital assets.</p>

<h3 id="economic-impacts-of-bitcoin-halving">Economic Impacts of Bitcoin Halving</h3>

<p>Changes in Mining Rewards and Their Economic Implications The recent halving of Bitcoin mining rewards from 6.25 to 3.125 bitcoins per block represents a pivotal shift in the economic landscape of cryptocurrency mining.</p>

<p>This reduction directly impacts the profitability of mining operations, as the reward for the computational power and energy expended decreases by half.</p>

<p>Historically, such reductions have incentivized miners to seek more energy-efficient technologies or cheaper energy sources to maintain profitability.</p>

<p>Additionally, the halving can lead to increased transaction fees as miners look to supplement their earnings, potentially influencing Bitcoin’s attractiveness as a transaction medium.</p>

<h2 id="effect-on-the-mining-industry-and-related-sectors">Effect on the Mining Industry and Related Sectors</h2>

<p>The halving event extends its economic effects beyond individual miners to the broader mining industry, including hardware manufacturers and energy suppliers.</p>

<p>The demand for advanced mining rigs typically increases as miners seek to offset the reduced rewards with more efficient hardware.</p>

<p>This surge in demand can boost the revenues for mining hardware companies but also leads to increased competition and innovation within the sector.</p>

<p>On the energy front, regions with lower electricity costs may see a rise in mining activities, which can have mixed effects on local economies and energy grids.</p>

<h3 id="long-term-economic-forecasts-post-halving">Long-Term Economic Forecasts Post-Halving</h3>

<p>Looking ahead, the long-term economic implications of Bitcoin’s latest halving are generally viewed with optimism.</p>

<p>Analysts predict that the reduced supply of new bitcoins entering the market will exert upward pressure on prices, assuming demand remains steady or increases.</p>

<p>This potential for higher future prices could attract new hodlers and sustain interest among existing ones, despite the immediate post-halving price drop.</p>

<p>Moreover, as Bitcoin continues to gain recognition as a ‘digital gold,’ its role in investment portfolios is likely to evolve, possibly influencing broader financial markets and economic policies.</p>

<h2 id="market-trends-following-the-halving">Market Trends Following the Halving</h2>

<p>The recent Bitcoin halving has triggered a series of market reactions and price fluctuations, drawing comparisons with previous events and eliciting varied perspectives from analysts.</p>

<p>Understanding these dynamics offers insights into the cryptocurrency’s resilience and the sentiment driving its ecosystem.</p>

<h3 id="immediate-market-reactions-and-price-fluctuations">Immediate Market Reactions and Price Fluctuations</h3>

<p>The immediate aftermath of the Bitcoin halving saw a mere 4% drop in its price.</p>

<p>This short term decline was contrary to the expected bullish trend typically associated with halving events, where reduced supply often leads to price increases.</p>

<p>Market participants appeared to react cautiously, possibly influenced by broader economic conditions and the overbought state of Bitcoin prior to the halving.</p>

<p>This initial drop has been a focal point for traders and hodlers trying to gauge the short-term volatility induced by such significant events.</p>

<h3 id="comparison-with-previous-halving-events">Comparison with Previous Halving Events</h3>

<p>Historically, Bitcoin halvings have been precursors to substantial bull runs. For instance, the 2016 halving event was followed by a dramatic increase in Bitcoin’s price over the next year.</p>

<p>However, the current scenario seems to diverge from this pattern, if we take into account the first week. Confirming ones’ confirmation bias never gets old.</p>

<p>Unlike previous events where a price surge was almost immediate and sustained, the current response has been more subdued and mixed.</p>

<p>This deviation may be attributed to a more mature market, greater regulatory scrutiny, and a more significant presence of institutional hodlers, which could lead to different dynamics than those observed in earlier cycles.</p>

<h2 id="analyst-perspectives-and-market-sentiment">Analyst Perspectives and Market Sentiment</h2>

<p>Despite the initial price drop, many analysts remain optimistic about Bitcoin’s long-term value. They argue that while the halving may not have caused an immediate price surge, it
sets the stage for future gains as the reduced supply could lead to higher prices if demand remains constant or increases.</p>

<p>Furthermore, analysts highlight the growing comparison of Bitcoin to ‘digital gold’, suggesting its potential as a hedge against inflation and currency devaluation in uncertain economic times.</p>

<p>However, there is also a cautious sentiment prevailing among some hodlers, driven by concerns over regulatory changes, the impact of new technologies on Bitcoin’s utility, and the broader economic environment affecting investment flows into cryptocurrencies.</p>

<p>Overall, the market trends post-halving paint a complex picture of Bitcoin’s position in the financial landscape, influenced by historical precedents, evolving market structures, and diverse analyst opinions.</p>

<p>This concludes the first part of my armchair analysis of the Bitcoin Halving. You can read the <a href="/deciphering-the-ripple-effects/">second part here</a></p>

<p><strong>Tip:</strong> Remember to appreciate the little things in life, <strong>stay humble &amp; stack sats.</strong> And if you liked my armchair analysis you <a href="https://strike.me/warped/">can send some sats my way</a></p>]]></content><author><name>alx</name></author><category term="Analysis" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is Part One of my armchair analysis on short term speculator sentiment following the halving. It is followed by Part Two, that you can find here.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/9.webp" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/images/9.webp" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Gamedev Is Not A Crime</title><link href="/gamedev-is-not-a-crime/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Gamedev Is Not A Crime" /><published>2024-03-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-03-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/gamedev-is-not-a-crime</id><content type="html" xml:base="/gamedev-is-not-a-crime/"><![CDATA[<p>Have you noticed that there are countless Pong, or Snake, or Froggie clones in the app stores ?</p>

<p>The proliferation of those games is taking place because they are the first test games that any aspiring developer starts from.</p>

<p>They are the proving grounds for most of us who start experimenting in this wonderfull world and those games will be the first modded works that their developers will work on.</p>

<p>They’re not meant to be full, complete, buggless or anything. The only function they carry is helping a developer learn the ropes.</p>

<p>Now, is that all it takes ? Obviously not.</p>

<p>I made a Pong clone uning Python classes, one with Pygame, one with GDevelop, one with UPBGE and now I’m working on one in Unity.</p>

<p>I find it to be a great tool that allows me as a noob to gauge how good of an understanding I have of various concepts.</p>

<p>I also did that with my programming languages journey. When I would learn to do a new thing in Python, I would then repeat the same thing in C++ or C.</p>

<p>PS I’m trying to get into jQuery these days, <em>without a functioning knowledge of Javascript</em>. This should be illegal…</p>]]></content><author><name>alx</name></author><category term="Rants" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you noticed that there are countless Pong, or Snake, or Froggie clones in the app stores ?]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/8.webp" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/images/8.webp" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Unfazed By War</title><link href="/unfazed-by-war/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Unfazed By War" /><published>2024-03-14T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-03-14T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/unfazed-by-war</id><content type="html" xml:base="/unfazed-by-war/"><![CDATA[<p>War, the master engineer of humanity. The greatest plight and solution of last -or first for some- resort. Wars are changing in the 21st century.</p>

<p>From the AI powered drones wreaking havoc to the Russian invaders of Ukrainian lands to the non-kinetic force that Bitcoin projects, the future of war is being redrawn.</p>

<p>Stack harder anon, this future looks bleak.</p>]]></content><author><name>alx</name></author><category term="Rants" /><category term="News" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[War, the master engineer of humanity. The greatest plight and solution of last -or first for some- resort. Wars are changing in the 21st century.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/7.webp" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/images/7.webp" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Whale Feeding Grounds</title><link href="/whale-feeding-grounds/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Whale Feeding Grounds" /><published>2024-03-02T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-03-02T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/whale-feeding-grounds</id><content type="html" xml:base="/whale-feeding-grounds/"><![CDATA[<p>It would make sense, wouldn’t it ? We’re a species that thrives in social circumstances. So, we all love seeing a comeback, either an underdog claiming a rightful spot or a green dildo. Bitcoin loves its green dildoes more than it loves stability. It thrives in volatility and so do we speculators.</p>

<p>The trend is your friend. Learning how to read the weather is an essential skill for any sailor, surfer or pilot. It could not be different for plebs riding the waves in this irrational market.</p>

<h2 id="do-you-want-to-feel-the-waves-">Do you want to feel the waves ?</h2>

<p>That’s all you have to ask yourself and dive right in.</p>

<p>You can dive in the testnet if you’re so inclined but really, is there a better rush than feeling the whales breathing down your back while you’re scalping buys in front of them at x100 ?</p>

<p>No, there isn’t and that’s why you’re a degenerate dark tetrad looking for a shortcut to the fucking moon.</p>]]></content><author><name>alx</name></author><category term="Rants" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[It would make sense, wouldn’t it ? We’re a species that thrives in social circumstances. So, we all love seeing a comeback, either an underdog claiming a rightful spot or a green dildo. Bitcoin loves its green dildoes more than it loves stability. It thrives in volatility and so do we speculators.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/1.webp" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/images/1.webp" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Riding The Red Waves</title><link href="/riding-the-red-waves/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Riding The Red Waves" /><published>2024-02-28T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-02-28T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/riding-the-red-waves</id><content type="html" xml:base="/riding-the-red-waves/"><![CDATA[<p>Sometimes the markets don’t go the way you want them. It’s okay, we’ve all been there. In fact, you MUST get there if you want to reach the moon in due time. Learning to deal with problems and liquidations is one of the most important aspects of trading.</p>

<p>It’s hard to resist the FOMO, but fear not for I will teach you the Art Of Zen in the land of Falling Knives.</p>

<p>I remember one time, I was part of a trading bot beta team, so before each release we’d receive the updated algo to go ahead and try it. So I armed it with my strategy, gave it its marching orders and sent it off to take over the Poloniex markets. Unaware, I looked after it for a bit and went on with my daily chores. Oh boy…</p>

<p>So, back then <a href="https://poloniex.com">Poloniex</a> had decent volumes, a nice shitcoin portfolio and an awesome lending market. So I had a trading bot running the markets and a lending bot lending out coins to speculators, it was awesome. But, unbeknownst to me, the trading bot was flawed. It had an issue in its logic. It was illogical.</p>

<p>I came back a few hours later to find 2.5 BTC spread in over 20 shitcoins. It was devastating and painful.</p>

<p>Eventually, and luckily for me, the market recovered and I more than quadrupled those coins in that month. But only because I was lucky. I decided that algos needed to be better overwatched by yours truly and that I should never let one manage the trades on its own.</p>]]></content><author><name>alx</name></author><category term="Trading" /><category term="Tips" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes the markets don’t go the way you want them. It’s okay, we’ve all been there. In fact, you MUST get there if you want to reach the moon in due time. Learning to deal with problems and liquidations is one of the most important aspects of trading.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/4.webp" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/images/4.webp" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Waiting For Summer</title><link href="/waiting-for-summer/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Waiting For Summer" /><published>2024-02-16T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-02-16T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/waiting-for-summer</id><content type="html" xml:base="/waiting-for-summer/"><![CDATA[<p>As the Bull Season (TM) is approaching many are feeling the FOMO. I’ve been here since 2013 and let me tell you, there is nothing quite like it. Especially if you lack the absolute minimum of self-respect.</p>

<p>The idea that yuo can spend $1 and become a gazillionaire overnight is overwhelming, more so among the plebs. So how do you do it ?</p>

<p>Enter x100. Add a touch of degeneracy, sprinkle it with Discrete Log Contracts and Bitcoin and you have something going.</p>

<p>Pair it with instant settlement on the Lightning Network and we’re golden baby, let’s send this rocket to the moon !</p>]]></content><author><name>alx</name></author><category term="Cope" /><category term="Rants" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the Bull Season (TM) is approaching many are feeling the FOMO. I’ve been here since 2013 and let me tell you, there is nothing quite like it. Especially if you lack the absolute minimum of self-respect.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/3.webp" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/images/3.webp" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Debugging The Bull</title><link href="/debugging-the-bull/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Debugging The Bull" /><published>2024-01-22T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-01-22T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/debugging-the-bull</id><content type="html" xml:base="/debugging-the-bull/"><![CDATA[<p>I always felt intrigued by <code>code</code>. It felt like the people who delved into its secrets held the keys to the magical kingdom of do-whatever-you-feel-like. And it really is like that, as Satoshi proved. He used merely 200k lines of C++ and rewrote the future.</p>

<p>And the plebs took that and memed a world reserve currency in existence. The lesson is clear: Don’t mess with the deranged.</p>

<p>Code snippets are always fun, even if they’re mostly useless:</p>

<figure class="highlight"><pre><code class="language-ruby" data-lang="ruby"><span class="k">def</span> <span class="nf">print_hi</span><span class="p">(</span><span class="nb">name</span><span class="p">)</span>
  <span class="nb">puts</span> <span class="s2">"Hi, </span><span class="si">#{</span><span class="nb">name</span><span class="si">}</span><span class="s2">"</span>
<span class="k">end</span>
<span class="n">print_hi</span><span class="p">(</span><span class="s1">'Satoshi'</span><span class="p">)</span>
<span class="c1">#=&gt; prints 'Hi, Satoshi' to STDOUT.</span></code></pre></figure>

<p>Fun. Code is fun, even if sometimes it’s merely a black box.</p>]]></content><author><name>alx</name></author><category term="Algos" /><category term="Code" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[I always felt intrigued by code. It felt like the people who delved into its secrets held the keys to the magical kingdom of do-whatever-you-feel-like. And it really is like that, as Satoshi proved. He used merely 200k lines of C++ and rewrote the future.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/6.webp" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/images/6.webp" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">x100 To The Moon</title><link href="/x100-to-the-moon/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="x100 To The Moon" /><published>2024-01-12T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-01-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/x100-to-the-moon</id><content type="html" xml:base="/x100-to-the-moon/"><![CDATA[<p>The first time I heard about Bitcoin, i was like “GTFO, computer money can’t work”. Since then I realized many shared the same first reaction. I guess it’s only natural. But since then, it has been a decade, and we know more about this unique form of technology.</p>

<p>I made my first million by 23 and lost it by 24, all thanks to Bitcoin, FOMO and hype. But I learned and I am stronger, a pleb among plebs. While WW3 is flaring up, we memed a world reserve currency in existence. Are you not entertained ?</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>If you don’t believe me or dont get it, I dont have time to convince you, sorry</p>
</blockquote>

<p>Let’s get x100 to the moon!</p>]]></content><author><name>alx</name></author><category term="bitcoin" /><category term="rants" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first time I heard about Bitcoin, i was like “GTFO, computer money can’t work”. Since then I realized many shared the same first reaction. I guess it’s only natural. But since then, it has been a decade, and we know more about this unique form of technology.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/2.webp" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/images/2.webp" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">History Rhymes, Doesn’t Repeat</title><link href="/history-rhymes-doesnt-repeat/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="History Rhymes, Doesn’t Repeat" /><published>2023-12-27T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-12-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/history-rhymes-doesnt-repeat</id><content type="html" xml:base="/history-rhymes-doesnt-repeat/"><![CDATA[<p>I’m not even going to try to pretend that I can make sense of what’s been happening in the last five years. And I don’t mean just <mark>Bitcoin</mark>.</p>

<p>I mean the “Two Weeks To Flatten The Curve” that drove so many people mad. Three years later and I can see people going completley off the rails.</p>

<p>Conspiracies are everywhere now and “They” control every aspect of life. The smoothbrains have taken over social media, made groups, are lobbying and even have people in national parliaments.</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>We are prone to let our mental life become invaded by legions of half truths, prejudices, and propaganda. At this point, I often wonder whether or not education is fulfilling its purpose. A great majority of the so-called educated people do not think logically and scientifically.</p>
</blockquote>

<p>Can we come out of this rabbit hole of stupidity ?</p>]]></content><author><name>alx</name></author><category term="News" /><category term="Cope" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m not even going to try to pretend that I can make sense of what’s been happening in the last five years. And I don’t mean just Bitcoin.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/assets/images/5.webp" /><media:content medium="image" url="/assets/images/5.webp" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry></feed>